Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Specialist Annual Reports, 1917-1968; 4
  - Home Economics; Alberta Johnston, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Home Economics; Louise Shunk, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Home Economics; Alberta B. Johnston, 1962 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Home Economics; Louise Shunk, 1962-1963 (Box 82, Folder 20-21)
  - Home Management; Gladys Branagun, 1921 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Home Management; Lottie Milam, 1921 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Home Management; Lottie Milan, Gertrude Hoffman, 1923 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Home Management; Gertrude Hoffman, 1924 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Home Management; Gertrude Hoffman, E. Miriam Hawkins, 1925 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Home Management; E. Miriam Hawkins, 1926-1927 (Box 82, Folder 27-28)
  - Home Management; E. Miriam Hawkins, Edith A. Sloan, 1928 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Home Management; Edith Sloan, Nora Hulbush, 1929 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Supplement to, Home Management, 1930 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Home Management; Nora L. Hulbush, 1930-1932 (Box 82, Folder 32-34)
  - Home Management; Mrs. Nora Chalkley, Oona Stautz, 1933 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Home Management; Oona Stautz, 1934-1935 (Box 82, Folder 36-37)
  - Home Management; Oona Stautz, Margaret H. Tulller, 1936 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Home Management; Margaret H. Tuller, 1937 (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Home Management; Margaret H. Tuller, 1938 (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Home Management; Mrs. Margaret H. Tuller, 1939-1941 (Box 82, Folder 41-43)
  - Home Management; Mrs. Margaret H. Tuller, 1942 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Home Management, 1942 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Home Management; Mrs. Margaret H. Tuller, 1943-1945 (Box 83, Folder 3-5)
  - Home Management; Downs, Fisher, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Home Management; Ermina Fisher, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Home Management; Margaret H. Tuller, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Home Management; Ermina Fisher, Marjorie E. Downs, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Field Reports, Home Management; Ermina Fisher, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Home Management; Miss Ermina Fisher, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Home Management; Ermina Fisher, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Home Management; Ermina Fisher, Mae Farris, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris, Ermina Fisher, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris, Eleanor Wilson, 1953-1955 (Box 83, Folder 16-18)
  - Home Management; Mae F. True, Eleanor F. Wilson, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Home Management; Mae F. True, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris True, Agnes Sunnell, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Home Management; Agnes Sunnell, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris True, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Home Management; Mae F. True, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Home Management; Alberta Johnston, 1960-1961 (Box 83, Folder 25-26)
  - Horticulture; H. M. Jennison, 1920-1921 (Box 83, Folder 27-28)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, 1926-1946 (Box 83, Folder 29-53)
  - Horticulture; John P. Drummond, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 54)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 55)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, John P. Drummond, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 56)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, 1948 (Box 83, Folder 57)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, Leonard Yager, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 58)
  - Horticulture; O. M. Patten, 1949 (Box 83, Folder 59)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, Leonard Yager, F. M. Harrington, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 60)
  - Horticulture; O. M. Patten, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 61-62)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, Leonard Yager, F. M. Harrington, 1951 (Box 83, Folder 63)
  - Horticulture; E. E. Isaac, Leonard Yager, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 64)
  - Horticulture; O. M. Patten, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 65)
  - Horticulture; Leonard Yager, 1953-1956 (Box 83, Folder 66-69)
  - Horticulture; Leonard Yager, Orville W. McCarver, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 70)
  - Horticulture; Orville W. McCarver, Robert A. Wearne, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 71)
  - Horticulture; Orville McCarver, Robert A. Wearne, 1959-1960 (Box 83, Folder 72-73)
  - Horticulture; Orville McCarver, 1961-1967 (Box 83, Folder 74-80)
  - Horticulture; O. W. McCarver, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 81)
  - Indian Extension; Verne Dusenberry, 1957 (Box 83, Folder 82)
  - Irrigation; Blaine Ferguson, 1921-1922 (Box 84, Folder 1-2)
  - Irrigation; G. H. Bingham, 1936-1945 (Box 84, Folder 3-12)
  - Irrigation; H. L. Dusenberry, 1948-1951 (Box 84, Folder 13-16)
  - Irrigation; Stanley Howard, 1952-1953 (Box 84, Folder 17-18)
  - Irrigation; Howard, Dusenberry, 1954-1956 (Box 84, Folder 19-21)
  - Irrigation; Stanley Howard, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 22-23)
  - Irrigation; Stanley W. Howard, 1959-1961 (Box 84, Folder 24-26)
  - Land Economist; H. G. Bolster, R. B. Tootell, 1934 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Land Economist; H. G. Bolster, 1935-1938 (Box 84, Folder 28-31)
  - Livestock; W. J. Hartman, 1917 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Livestock; E. H. Riley, 1919 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Livestock; R. B. Millin, 1921-1924 (Box 84, Folder 34-37)
  - Livestock; R. L. Waddell, 1925-1927 (Box 84, Folder 38-40)
  - Livestock; D. E. Richards, R. L. Waddell, 1928 (Box 84, Folder 41)
  - Livestock; D. E. Richards, 1929-1930 (Box 84, Folder 42-43)
  - Livestock; I. M. C. Anderson, 1932 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Livestock; D. E. Richards, 1932 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Livestock; I. M. C. Anderson, 1933-1936 (Box 85, Folder 3-6)
  - Livestock; Howard Lewis, I. M. C. Anderson, 1937 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Livestock; Howard G. Lewis, 1938 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Livestock; H. G. Lewis, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, 1940 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Livestock; H. G. Bolster, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Appendix to Annual Report; E. P. Orcutt, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Livestock; H. G. Bolster, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, 1942-1944 (Box 85, Folder 15-17)
  - Livestock; F. A. Ralston, 1945-1947 (Box 85, Folder 18-20)
  - Livestock; F. A. Ralston, E. P. Orcutt, 1948 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Livestock; Paul Orcutt, F. A. Ralston, 1949-1950 (Box 85, Folder 22-23)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, F. A. Ralston, N. A. Jacobsen, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, N. A. Jacobsen, 1952-1954 (Box 85, Folder 25-27)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, E. P. Orcutt, 1955 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, N. A. Jacobsen, 1956-1960 (Box 86, Folder 2-6)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, Paul Orcutt, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, James Drummond, 1962 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, 1963-1964 (Box 86, Folder 9-10)
  - Livestock; James Drummond, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, James Drummond, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Livestock; James Drummond, N. A. Jacobsen, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Marketing; W. L. Beers, 1917-1919 (Box 86, Folder 15-17)
  - Marketing; E. H. Riley, 1920 (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Marketing; John F. Ware, 1921 (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Marketing; C. C. Conser, 1930-1933 (Box 86, Folder 20-23)
  - Marketing; Bruce L. Brooks, 1950-1955 (Box 86, Folder 24-29)
  - Marketing; E. D. Vaughan, N. A. Jacobsen, E. P. Orcutt, A. O. Jacobs, Mary Loughead, 1957-1958 (Box 86, Folder 30-31)
  - Marketing; E. D. Vaughan, E. P. Orcutt, M. Louhead, N. A. Jacobsen, A. O. Jacobs, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 32)
  - Marketing; E. D. Vaughan, 1960-1962 (Box 86, Folder 33-35)
  - Marketing; Charles Rust, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 36)
  - Marketing; Ramon Sammons, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 37)
  - Marketing; Charles Rust, Robert Bucher, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 38)
  - Marketing; Charles Rust, James Cothern, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 39)
  - Out Look; Paul Carpenter, 1928-1934 (Box 87, Folder 1-6)
  - Out Look; Willard Lamphere, 1935-1939 (Box 87, Folder 7-11)
  - Plant Pathology; H. E. Morris, 1950-1955 (Box 87, Folder 12-17)
  - Plant Pathology; H. E. Morris, M. M. Afanasiev, 1956 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Plant Pathology; M. M. Afanasiev, Eugene L. Sharp, 1957-1959 (Box 87, Folder 19-21)
  - Plant Pathology; M. M. Afanasiev, Richard I. Hamilton, Eugene L. Sharp, 1960 (Box 87, Folder 22)
  - Plant Pathology; M. M. Afanasiev, R. I. Hamilton, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 23)
  - Plant Pathology; M. M. Afanasiev, 1962-1967 (Box 87, Folder 24-29)
  - Plant Pathology; Robert Carlstrom, 1968 (Box 87, Folder 30)
  - Poultry; R. L. Smith, 1919-1921 (Box 87, Folder 31-33)
  - Poultry; H. E. Cushman, 1922-1932 (Box 87, Folder 34-44)
  - Poultry; Harriette E. Cushman, 1933-1943 (Box 87, Folder 45-54)
  - Poultry; Harriette E. Cushman, 1944-1954 (Box 88, Folder 1-11)
  - Poultry; Edmund Guenthner, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Poultry; Edmund Guenthner, Glen Hart, 1956 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Poultry; Glen Hart, 1957-1958 (Box 88, Folder 14-15)
  - Project for Human Resource Development; Paul Moore, 1962-1966 (Box 88, Folder 16-18)
  - Project for Human Resource Development; Vivienne Kintz, 1967-1968 (Box 88, Folder 19-20)
  - Publications; R. B. Bowden, 1925-1929 (Box 88, Folder 21-24)
  - Publications, 1930-1931 (Box 88, Folder 25-26)
  - Publications; John Dexter, 1933-1934 (Box 88, Folder 27-28)
  - Publications; Louis G. True, 1935-1945 (Box 88, Folder 29-39)
  - Publications; L. True, H. M. White, 1946 (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Publications, 1947 (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - Publications; Louis True, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - Publications; Louis G. True, 1949 (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - Publications; Louis True, H. M. White, Mary L. Bretz, Russell Wilson, 1950 (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - Publications; L. G. True, H. M. White, Alys Reeder, R. J. Wilson, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - Publications; Louis G. True, H. M. White, Alys Reeder, Paul Jesswein, 1952-1953 (Box 88, Folder 46-47)
  - Publications; Louis G. True, H. M. White, Alys Reeder, Paul Jesswein, Marlow Urdahl, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 48)
  - Publications; Louis G. True, H. M. White, Iris Parker, Paul F. Jesswein, Marlow S. Urdahl, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 49)
  - Publications; Louis True, Herbert White, Les Kinzell, Mary Ketelsen, Paul Jesswein, 1956 (Box 88, Folder 50)
  - Publications; H. D. Berry, L. G. True, H. M. White, P. F. Jesswein, M. M. Maloney, L. Kinzell, 1957 (Box 88, Folder 51)
  - Publications; Louis True, H. M. White, Paul Jesswein, Mary Maloney, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 52)
  - Publications; Hardy D. Berry, Louis G. True, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 53)
  - Publications; Burl Winchester, 1962 (Box 88, Folder 54)
  - Publications; Burl Winchester, 1963 (Box 88, Folder 55)
  - Range Management; Ray G. Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 56-57)
  - Range Management; Karl G. Parker, 1952-1954 (Box 88, Folder 58-60)
  - Range Management; Karl G. Parker, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Range Management, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Range Management; Karl G. Parker, 1957-1961 (Box 89, Folder 3-7)
  - Range Management; Donald E. Ryerson, 1963-1966 (Box 89, Folder 8-11)
  - Range Management; Ned Jefferies, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Rodent Control, 1918 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Rodent Control; H. L. Seamans, 1919 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - Rodent Control, 1920 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - Rodent Control; A. E. Oman, 1921-1924 (Box 89, Folder 16-19)
  - Rodent Control; O. E. Stephl, 1925-1932 (Box 89, Folder 20-26)
  - Progress Reports, Rural Development, 1956-1959 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - Rural Development; Ravalli County, 1958 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Rural Development; Lake and Ravalli County, 1959 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Rural Development, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Rural Electrification; Armin J. Hill, 1938-1941 (Box 89, Folder 31-34)
  - Rural Firefighters Service; R. E. Bodley, 1946 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Rural Firefighters Service; Geo. W. Gustafson, 1947-1954 (Box 89, Folder 36-43)
  - Rural Firefighters Service; C. V. Rubottom, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 44)
  - Safety Farm and Home Program; J. C. Taylor, 1946-1949 (Box 89, Folder 45-48)
  - Soil Conservation; M. P. Hansmeier, 1937-1940 (Box 89, Folder 49-52)
  - Soil Conservation; Wayne L. Proff, 1941 (Box 89, Folder 53)
  - Soil Conservation; M. P. Hansmeier, 1941 (Box 89, Folder 54)
  - Soil Conservation; M. P. Hansmeier, 1942-1948 (Box 90, Folder 1-7)
  - Soil Conservation; M. P. Hansmeier, J. C. Taylor, 1949 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Soil Conservation; M. P. Hansmeier, B. W. Brink, 1950 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Soil Conservation; B. W. Brink, 1951 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Soil Conservation; Rex Campbell, 1952-1960 (Box 90, Folder 11-19)
  - Soils; Bernard L. Brown, 1958-1960 (Box 90, Folder 20-22)
  - Soils; Charles M. Smith, 1963 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Soils; Charles Smith, 1964-1966 (Box 90, Folder 24-26)
  - Chemical Education; M. J. Jackson, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - Soils; Charles Smith, 1967 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - Soils; Charles M. Smith, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Weed Control; Donald Luebbe, 1946-1947 (Box 90, Folder 30-31)
  - Weed Control; Robert Warden, H. L. Dusenberry, 1948 (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Weed Control; Robert Warden, 1949-1958 (Box 90, Folder 33-39)
  - Weed Control; Eugene Heikes, 1959-1961 (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
  - Weed Control; Leslie Sonder, 1962-1968 (Box 91, Folder 4-10)
- Administration, 1914-1970; 5
  Annual and monthly reports issued by the Montana Extension Service director and subordinate officers such as the county agent leader, home demonstration agent leader, and 4-H club leader. Some correspondence files are also present in this series. The folders in this series have been arranged alphabetically by the administrative officer's title, and then chronologically within that name sort. Occasionally the officer's name is included.
  - Extension Director, 1914-1916 (Box 91, Folder 11-12)
  - Extension Director Summary, 1916 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - Extension Director; F. S. Cooley, 1917-1920 (Box 91, Folder 14-17)
  - Farmer's Institute, 1920 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Extension Director; F. S. Cooley, 1921 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Farmer's Institute, 1921 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Extension Director; F. S. Cooley, 1922-1923 (Box 91, Folder 21-22)
  - Farmer's Institute, 1923 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Extension Director; J. C. Taylor, 1924-1945 (Box 91, Folder 24-45)
  - Extension Director; R. B. Tootell, 1946-1947 (Box 91, Folder 46-47)
  - Extension Director; R. B. Tootell, 1948-1952 (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
  - Extension Director; R. B. Tootell, N. E Beers, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Extension Director; N. E. Beers, 1954-1957 (Box 92, Folder 7-10)
  - Extension Director; Torlief Aasheim, 1958-1963 (Box 92, Folder 11-16)
  - County Agent Leader Monthly Reports, 1914-1915 (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - County Agent Leader; M. L. Wilson, 1915 (Box 92, Folder 18-19)
  - County Agent Leader Monthly Report, 1916 (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - County Agent Leader, 1916 (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - County Agent Leader Monthly Report, 1917 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - County Agent Leader; J. C. Taylor, 1917 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - County Agent Leader Plan for Special Service, 1917 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - County Agent Leader, 1918 January-1919 December (Box 92, Folder 25-48)
  - County Agent Leader; M. L. Wilson, 1919-1921 (Box 92, Folder 49-51)
  - County Agent Leader; Quarterly, 1921 (Box 92, Folder 52)
  - County Agent Leader, 1918-1921 (Box 92, Folder 53)
  - County Agent Leader; Quarterly, 1922 (Box 92, Folder 54)
  - County Agent Leader, 1922 (Box 92, Folder 55)
  - County Agent Leader; Statistical work, 1924 (Box 92, Folder 56)
  - County Agent Leader, 1925 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Totals for Extension Work, 1925 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - County Agent Leader; Fred Bennion, 1926-1932 (Box 93, Folder 3-9)
  - Facts About Extension Work, 1932 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - County Agent Leader, 1933 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - County Agent Leader; R. E. Bodley, 1934-1939 (Box 93, Folder 12-17)
  - Twenty Five Year Summary of Montana Extension Service (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - County Agent Leader; R. E. Bodley, 1940-1947 (Box 93, Folder 19-27)
  - County Agent Leader; N. E. Beers, 1947-1949 (Box 93, Folder 28-30)
  - County Agent Leader; N. E. Beers, 1950-1952 (Box 94, Folder 1-3)
  - County Agent Leader; Burl Winchester, 1953-1959 (Box 94, Folder 4-10)
  - County Agent Leader; Rex Campbell, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - County Agent Leader, 1961-1962 (Box 94, Folder 12-13)
  - County Agent Leader; R. F. Rasmusson, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - County Agent Leader; R. F. Rasmusson: Organization & Supervision, 1963 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - County Agent Leader; R. F. Rasmusson, 1964 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - County Agent Leader, 1968-1970 (Box 94, Folder 17-19)
  - Home Economics Weekly Reports (7/1/15-6/30/16); Katherine Jensen, 1915-1916 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Home Economics; Bess Rowe, 1916-1918 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Bess Rowe, 1919 (Box 94, Folder 22-23)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Bess Rowe, Blanche Lee, 1920 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Anna Turley, 1921 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Quarterly Report, 1922 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, 1922 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - District Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, 1923 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, Anna Turley, 1923 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, 1924-1927 (Box 94, Folder 30-33)
  - Home Demonstration Program; Blanche Lee, 1928 (Box 94, Folder 34)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, 1928 (Box 94, Folder 35)
  - Home Demonstration Program; Blanche Lee, 1929 (Box 94, Folder 36)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Blanche Lee, 1929-1935 (Box 94, Folder 37-43)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Frances Smith, 1936-1946 (Box 95, Folder 1-11)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Bessie McClelland, 1947-1960 (Box 95, Folder 12-25)
  - Home Demonstration Leader; Plan of Work, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Administration, N. E. Beers, 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 27-28)
  - Administration, Torlief Aasheim, 1959-1968 (Box 95, Folder 29-38)
  - Agricultural Chemicals; M. J. Jackson, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 1-2)
  - Agricultural Engineering; E. B. Wilson, 1953-1960 (Box 96, Folder 3-7)
  - Agricultural Production and Conservation; Donald Luebbe, 1961-1970 (Box 96, Folder 8-14)
  - Agricultural Production and Conservation; M. M. Afanasiev, 1965-1970 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Agricultural Production and Conservation; Donald Luebbe, 1966-1968 (Box 96, Folder 16-18)
  - Agronomy; Ralph Mercer, Arthur Shaw, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 19-22)
  - Agronomy; Arthur Shaw, 1964-1968 (Box 96, Folder 23-25)
  - Clothing and Textiles; Lora Hilyard, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 26-29)
  - Dairy and Swine; Arthur Jacobs, 1957-1959 (Box 96, Folder 30-32)
  - Dairy and Swine; Earl Pierce, 1960-1968 (Box 96, Folder 33-39)
  - Economics; John Bower, 1957-1959 (Box 96, Folder 37-29)
  - Economics; Robert Bucher, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 40-41)
  - Economics; James Cothern, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 42)
  - Entomology; J. H. Pepper, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 43-46)
  - Entomology; Ray Pratt, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 47)
  - Family Economics; Alberta Johnston, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 48)
  - Family Life; Amy Wold, 1957-1962 (Box 96, Folder 49-54)
  - Farm Management; M. E. Quenemoen, Warren Trock, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 55-58)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary Loughead, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 59-62)
  - Forestry; Richard Marks, 1958-1970 (Box 96, Folder 63-67)
  - 4-H; Paul Moore, Geraldine Fenn, C. W. Vaughn, 1957-1960 (Box 96, Folder 68-71)
  - Health; Frances Macdonald, 1953-1956 (Box 96, Folder 72-75)
  - Home Economics; Louise Shunk, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 76)
  - Summary of Home Economics Programs, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 77)
  - Home Economics; Louise Shunk, 1962-1963 (Box 96, Folder 78-79)
  - Home Economics; Vivienne Kintz, 1964-1966 (Box 96, Folder 80-82)
  - Home Management; Mae Farris, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 83)
  - Home Management; Mae True, 1956-1958 (Box 96, Folder 84-86)
  - Home Management; Agnes Sunnell, 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 87-88)
  - Horticulture; Leonard Yager, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 89)
  - Horticulture; Orville McCarver, 1958-1959 (Box 96, Folder 90-91)
  - Horticulture; Robert Wearne, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 92)
  - Horticulture; Orville McCarver, 1960-1968 (Box 96, Folder 93-96)
  - Housing and Furnishings; Mae True, 1959-1960 (Box 96, Folder 97-98)
  - Human Resource Development; Burl Winchester, 1961-1962 (Box 97, Folder 1-2)
  - Human Resource Development; Paul Moore, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 3-6)
  - Human Resource Development; Vivienne Kintz, 1967-1968 (Box 97, Folder 7-8)
  - Information; Herb White, Davidson, True, Reeder, Urdahl, Jesswein, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Information; Herb White, Davidson, True, Urdahl, Jesswein, 1956 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Information; Herb White, Davidson, True, Jesswein, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Information; Hardy Berry, 1958-1960 (Box 97, Folder 12-14)
  - Information; Burl Winchester, 1961-1970 (Box 97, Folder 15-19)
  - Information; Sam Rosen, 1966-1968 (Box 97, Folder 20-22)
  - Irrigation, Stanley Howard, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 23-26)
  - Livestock; E. P. Orcutt, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 27-30)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, 1964 (Box 97, Folder 31-32)
  - Livestock; Burl Winchester, 1967 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Livestock; James Drummond, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Livestock; N. A. Jacobsen, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - Marketing; E. D. Vaughan, 1957-1962 (Box 97, Folder 36-42)
  - Marketing; Charles Rust, 1963-1970 (Box 97, Folder 43-46)
  - Marketing Information for Consumers; Mary Loughead, 1959-1960 (Box 97, Folder 47-48)
  - Organization and Supervision of County Extension Agents; R. F. Rasmusson, 1962-1970 (Box 97, Folder 49-52)
  - Plant Pathology; H. E. Morris, 1957 (Box 97, Folder 53)
  - Plant Pathology; M. M. Afanasiev, 1958-1967 (Box 97, Folder 54-58)
  - Poultry; Harriet Cushman, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 59-60)
  - Poultry; Edmund Guenthner, 1956 (Box 97, Folder 61)
  - Poultry; Glen Hart, 1957-1958 (Box 97, Folder 62-63)
  - Poultry; George Davis, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 64)
  - Problems and Situations Considered in the 1962 Plans of Work; Central District (Box 97, Folder 65)
  - Problems and Situations Considered in the 1962 Plans of Work; Eastern District (Box 97, Folder 66)
  - Problems and Situations Considered in the 1962 Plans of Work; Western District (Box 97, Folder 67)
  - Public Affairs and Community Development; J Glenn Jones, 1961 (Box 97, Folder 68)
  - Public Affairs and Community Development; John Bower, 1962-1970 (Box 97, Folder 69-75)
  - Range Management; Karl Parker, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 76-79)
  - Range Management; Donald Ryerson, 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 80-81)
  - Rural Firefighters; George Gustafson, 1949-1953 (Box 97, Folder 82-86)
  - Soil Conservation; Rex Campbell, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 87-90)
  - Soils; Bernard Brown, 1959-1960 (Box 97, Folder 91-92)
  - Soils; Charles Smith, 1964-1967 (Box 97, Folder 93-95)
  - State Home Demonstration Leaders; Bessie McClelland, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 96-99)
  - Supervisory Department; N. E. Beers, 1951-1953 (Box 97, Folder 100-102)
  - Supervisory Department; Burl Winchester, 1955-1960 (Box 97, Folder 103-108)
  - Supervisory Department; R. F. Rassmusson, 1961-1964 (Box 97, Folder 109-112)
  - Training Leader; Harry Cosgriffe, 1957-1960 (Box 97, Folder 113-115)
  - Veterinary Science; Howard Welch, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 116-117)
  - Veterinary Science; E. A. Tunnicliff, 1953-1955 (Box 97, Folder 118-120)
  - Weed Control; Eugene Heikes, 1957-1960 (Box 98, Folder 1-4)
  - Weed Control; Leslie Sonder, 1964-1968 (Box 98, Folder 5-7)
  - Wildlife; Eldon Smith, 1957-1967 (Box 98, Folder 8-14)
  - Young Adult Work; J. C. Taylor, 1946-1948 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Young Farm and Homemakers; J. C. Taylor, 1948 (Box 98, Folder 16)